To all of my... yeah,
My sincere gratitude to every of you.
You have completed me and guided me.
You have changed me and loved me.
You have provided me with wonderful opportunities.
You have made me happy.
You have empowered me, admired and appreciated me.
Thank you very much.
My sincere gratitude to every of you.
You have completed me and guided me.
You have changed me and loved me.
You have provided me with wonderful opportunities.
You have made me happy.
You have empowered me, admired and appreciated me.
Thank you very much.
This is for all who had loved me.
This is for all who had brought happiness to me.
This is for all who had changed me.
This is for all who had empowered me.
I am sincerely grateful for every of you,
who has  completed me and loved me.
Thank you very much.
who has completed me and loved me.